How difficult do you think it would be for them to destroy the vanguard party if they couldn't tell the vanguard party from the community?
Because we're all doing the exact same thing.
How difficult is that?
Like, so that's what and that's the power of four wins.
You have a Panther Party chapter, a Black Panther Party chapter operating within the community that they live in that's following these principles.
When you look from the outside, it all look like the same thing.
Which which one of these guys is Doc Molotov?
I don't know because they're all teaching classes, because they're all out here putting in the labor to uplift this community.
So now I don't know who's a Panther, who's not.
If they're not wearing the logo, I have no idea who they are.
And the citizens are depending on the system.
It looks like Pantherville.
I don't know what's going on.
I'm just saying it's a deeper strategy behind it because when you start thinking about, okay, let's put it this way.
Let's look at the reality of the situation, right?
The reality of the situation is, and I love, Doc, I got to applaud you for how you've been able to dance around saying,
I've been serving things since we've been on here, but I'm going to just say this because fuck it.
Why not?
The reality of the matter is this.
A, people are going to start starving.
People are going to start growing food.
B, people's houses are going to start getting taken by the government.
So they're going to have to start building new houses for themselves.
C, the schools are teaching your children to be robots.
At some point, you're going to realize this and take them out.
Then you have to teach them.
Once you start doing all of those things, much like you said, Greg, they're coming.
Now what do you do?
The reality is political power has never been in the ballot box.
Political power is probably sitting in your fucking holster and you're scared to use it.
And sitting there, you're scared to use it because throughout history, we've been way more comfortable using it on each other.
And I don't just mean black people when I stay on each other.
I mean, citizens have been far more comfortable with utilizing their armaments against one another as opposed to the ones who are actually oppressing their communities.
I'll never understand that concept.
Ever.
You know who I have big love for?
And it's going to sound crazy when I say this because of who I am.
But I'll tell you who I got love for.
It's a very twisted kind of love.
Let me be clear about that.
I got big love for gangs.
I love them.
I talk to them all the time.
You know why?
Because I'm trying to turn that love from being a twisted love into the picture it was supposed to be when it started.
The reality is they have a better concept of community defense than most people who live in any community ever will.
There's a gang in South Central L.A. that I talk to.
And one thing about them that I always think about when it comes to respect is that they told me that it's very difficult for anybody who's a child predator to be in that neighborhood because they take care of them.
And there's a code that they live by and they don't allow pimping.
And to me, I'm thinking to myself, wait a minute.
So a gang in South Central L.A. is doing more to stop crime than law enforcement and government.
And it just shows that it's a system that works and there's a mutual respect.
That's a form of community.
That's a form of consequence that is outside the law, outside government.
And I'm thinking to myself, if gangs can do that, imagine what we could do if neighborhoods started to see themselves as fortresses rather than just, oh, I just live in this house in this neighborhood.
I don't know my neighbors.
It's like, imagine if that neighborhood becomes your fortress.
You can feel safe.
You know you're protected.
You know that your neighbor's got your back.
The fact of the matter is the odds are on our side.
They're terrified of our power.
That's why they're investing so much in psyops, in divisions, in racism, in political messaging.
That's why they're investing so much in surveillance, because they know that the United States specifically has potentially holds the largest revolutionary armed force known to man.
80 million Americans own guns.
We got our asses kicked in Afghanistan from 70,000 Taliban.
We got our asses kicked in Vietnam.
Hamas was able to, with only, what, 40,000 members, was able to withstand the entire might of the Israeli military and thus the U.S. military in the past two years through tunnels and old school methods.
You're talking about a ratio of 11 to 1.
The most that the federal government can muster is 2.2 million.
That's including the janitors who are federal.
Versus 80 million armed Americans, 2.2 million of those are trained snipers who go hunting out in the backwoods and can survive.
I think the janitor's going to be on our side.
Right.
The janitor's going to be on our side.
That's if they can muster, like, all the federal forces, which they probably won't, especially if the people are together.
I just lament the fact that, like, a lot of these 2A guys are like, I love two things, outlaw country and the law.
Back to blue, baby.
But I think as, like, material conditions continue to degrade, I'm not wrong, okay?
Yo, that might be the funniest thing I heard all day.
I'm sorry.
Dude, we went from, like, Obama's going to bring in a police state to, hey, bring on the police state because of the branding.
So my thing is, if branding is all it takes, then that's what the left needs to focus on.
Let's focus on the branding of this because theory ain't going to cut it.
It could be the most logical plan on the planet.
It doesn't matter unless you control the branding, which is why I came up with the acronym U8, Unite Against the Elites.
Because even your most racist motherfucker in the backwoods of Alabama, if you were to ask him, hey, do you believe that elites are fucking over all of our lives?
They'll say yes.
Okay, boom.
Common ground.
Do you want to do something about it?
The racism and the deprogramming from racism, that's going to be an ongoing process.
But at least we can get them on board with the thought that you are getting fucked over just like the black person is getting fucked over.
We're all victims, whether or not we're going to get along ideologically or whatever.
We're all should be on the same page for this shit.
And that's why United Against the Elites is like the most universal concept as far as like acronym I can come up with.
What I've always found easier about people on the right, even with problematic like social ideas, is that they know they're being played.
You know, a lot of these establishment people who I've been fighting with online for messaging are like liberals who think that the system is inherently good and they just need their faith to be restored in it.
And it can be reformed through progressive political change.
So that's going to be a challenge.
But, you know, I think some of them are starting to realize, especially now that like Mom Donnie has been reversing on a lot of his positions.
Let's talk about that, Bruce.
I'm sorry.
Please go ahead.
I can't help it.
It's hilarious.
No, listen.
When you know something, when you know something, and then you see it, you just be like, ah, there you go.
I was telling Greg earlier, I was like, do you know who Mom Donnie is?
He's that toy that your kid really wants that you know is just like going to break and be a piece of shit.
And you tell your kid, hey, like, don't get this toy.
It's not going to work.
But your kid really wants it.
You're like, all right, unless I get this toy for my kid, he's not going to shut up about it.
So you go and buy that toy just so that it can break, just so he can finally be like, all right, did you learn your lesson now?
Can we just end this conversation?
Nobody's coming to save us.
It's not a bad analogy at all.
When you have somebody who's going to go out and calling themselves a socialist, right, and then go and talk about how, you know, Maduro is this horrible dictator, right?
At a time when we're ramping up to invade Venezuela, it seems like, right, or to, you know, engage in some sort of military conflict with them.
When we're blockading Venezuela, when we're, you know, airstriking their ships, right, and you have somebody who calls themselves a socialist but is spouting rhetoric that actually helps to sell that, right?
Like, that is a betrayal of socialist, you know, ideals.
That is a complete betrayal of the revolution, and that's helping the ruling class drag us into war, right?
You know, you want to talk about somebody being a dictator, right?
Again, you know, Maduro is giving the citizens firearms, right?
He's handing out rifles.
It's the most patriotic shit I've ever seen in my life.
What would happen to all the 2A people?
Like, anyone who's second amendment should be demanding that our government gives every able-bodied citizen a rifle, right?
Gives everybody, every adult who wants one a rifle, right?
Unless we are less free in this country than they are in Venezuela, unless there is more dissatisfaction against the government than there is in a dictatorship, right?
There is no political reason for them not to hand us all rifles.
Why can't they do that?
Because it's more of a dictatorship here.
That's why.
Have you seen videos coming out of Venezuela right now of them training civilians, big people who are just average, like, 70-year-old ladies shooting an AK-47 and learning how to survive?
I'm like, that's the most community, like, hardcore patriotism I've ever seen in my entire life.
What the hell are we doing?
They want to silence, silence, so we're riding with the silence, silence.